

**ACCOUNTS & FINANCE** 

#### **Details**

Orce Nikolov 104
Kavadarci, 1430
North Macedonia
076957190
slavica\_zlatevska@yahoo.com

DRIVING LICENSE

B-category

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

19.10.1993 Kavadarci

### **Profile**

I have over 5 years of accounting work experience. I am an accomplished communicator, with excellent organizational, decision making, and time management skills and have a proven track record of consistently meeting and regularly surpassing demanding performance goals.

Manage invoicing, outgoing and ingoing, expense reports, cash flows, VAT report, monthly reconciliation, activities for reporting, end-year activities. Directly interacting with customers and vendors if needed.

I am very organized person who is always trying to finish things on time. I am quick learner and positive person. Always open for learning new things. Team player who wants to take and give advice.

# **Employment History**

Finance and accounting, Crna Reka Petrol, Kavadarci

JULY 2016

-Finance, accounting and administrative activities

Activities in the credit department, Komercijalna Banka AD Skopje, Kavadarci

JULY 2013 - AUGUST 2013

Activities in the payment operations department, Komercijalna Banka AD Skopje

AUGUST 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014

Activities in the payment operations department, Sparkasse Bank, Kavadarci

JUNE 2015 - AUGUST 2015

### Education

Financial Management, Ss. Cyril and Methodius University in Skopje, Faculty of Economics-Skopje, Skopje

SEPTEMBER 2012 - JULY 2016

Bachelor of science in economics: University "Cyril and Methodius" - Faculty of Economics in, Skopje, R.Macedonia

2012 - 2016

Study program: ECTS

Department: Financial Management

Average: 8.81

Economic, legal and trade profession - economic technician, Secondary Education Dobri Daskalov High School - Kavadarci

## Courses

Certified logistics officer, Makam Transport

Skills for success, Pivara Skopje AD Motiva DOO

Accounting course, Atc Centre